{"data":[{"question":"I would wear my red dress if it ___ a stain in the front.","a":"had","b":"didn't have","c":"would have","d":"has","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 2: It is possible but very unlikely that the condition will be fulfilled. \n- Form: if + Simple Past, Conditional I (= would + Infinitive) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"Mary might have come to school in time for Professor Smith's lecture ___.","a":"if she got up earlier","b":"unless she had got up earlier","c":"but she got up rather late","d":"but she had gotten up so late","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Structur: Might + Have + PP, Past simple tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"We would have arrived sooner except we ___ a flat tire.","a":"had","b":"would have","c":"has not","d":"has","answer":"1","explain":"- Structure: Would + Have + PP, Past simple tense","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"I hope that you ___ all right.","a":"will be","b":"should be","c":"we re","d":"would be","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Hope\/ Wish + simple present: It is possible and also very likely that the condition will be fulfilled","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"How happy I ___, if you had been with me then.","a":"could be","b":"would have been","c":"should have been","d":"were","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 3: It is impossible that the condition will be fulfilled because it refers to the past. \n- Form: if + Past Perfect, Conditional II (= would + have + Past Participle) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"___ their assistance, he would have to lead a very miserable life; he might even starve to death.","a":"With","b":"But for","c":"Without for","d":"If not","answer":"2","explain":"\n- But for: used when you are saying that something would have happened if something or someone else had not prevented it","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"He might have led a life quite different from the one he lived ___ this event which happened all of a sudden.","a":"were it not for","b":"had it not been for","c":"if it were not for","d":"if there were not","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Had it not been for= if it hadn't been for \n- Conditional Sentence Type 3: It is impossible that the condition will be fulfilled because it refers to the past. \n- Form: if + Past Perfect, Conditional II (= would + have + Past Participle)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"As you know, I am a disabled man, but I should be very happy if I ___ of service to you.","a":"am","b":"have been","c":"could be","d":"would be","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Conditional Sentence Type 2: It is possible but very unlikely that the condition will be fulfilled. \n- Form: if + Simple Past, Conditional I (= would + Infinitive)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"It is proposed by some that the new method ___ adopted at once, but others say that they may be criticized if it ___ a failure.","a":"should be, were to prove","b":"is, would prove","c":"shall be, proved","d":"be, should prove","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Propose (that) + Verb (without to) \n- Conditional Sentence Type 2: It is possible but very unlikely that the condition will be fulfilled. \n- Form: if + Simple Past, Conditional I (= would + Infinitive) ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"},{"question":"He is already on the wrong side of the forties \" It's necessary that he ___ himself a wife and settled down.\"","a":"finds","b":"should find","c":"found","d":"had found","answer":"2","explain":"\n- It's necessary that someone should do something: used to give advice","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"50","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"1"}]}